Guide to the Edward H. Boos Photographs 1897-1907
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- Unidentified Lakes and Mountains, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-200)
- Mission Creek, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-201)
- Flowers, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-202)
- Flowers, black and white, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-203)
- Colorized flowers, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-204)
- View of bridge from river bank, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-205)
- Glacier Lake with its glaciers and abrupt cliff banks, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-206)
- Pend'Oreille Falls [near Polson, Montana], undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-207)
- Unidentified Hillside, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-208)
- Mission Range Panorama, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-209)
- Unidentified Waterfall, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-210)
- View of Flathead Lake Looking North from Polson Point with unidentified man, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-211)
- A Cloudy Day on Mission Creek, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-212)
- Unidentified Geyser, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-213)
- Unidentified Geyser, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-214)
- Unidentified People around geyser at unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-215)
- Missoula Mercantile Company, exterior corner of building, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-216)
- Man standing on top of Logging Wagon, Hamilton, 1900 (Box 4, Photo number 672-217)
- Men loading logs onto train, Hamilton, 1900 (Box 4, Photo number 672-218)
- Loaded logging cars; Log piles and clean cut in background, Hamilton, 1900 (Box 4, Photo number 672-219)
- Man on loaded logging wagon pulled by four horses, Hamilton, 1900 (Box 4, Photo number 672-220)
- Daly Ranch Horse, Full Horse, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-221)
- Forested area, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-222)
- Daly Ranch Horse and unidentified man, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-223)
- Daly Ranch Horse and unidentified man, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-224)
- Cattle, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-225)
- Unidentified Men and Harvesting Equipment, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-226)
- Unidentified Men Bailing Hay, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-227)
- Edward Boos?, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-228)
- Unidentified Women and Children, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-229)
- Unidentified Girls in Field, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-230)
- "City of Missoula", undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-231)
- General View of St. Ignatius Mission, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-232)
- St. Ignatius Mission Church, one of the largest in the west, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-233)
- Swans, Unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-234)
- Swans gathered near unidentified women, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-235)
- On Gold Stream, 14 miles from Victoria, B.C., undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-236)
- 25th Infantry Bicycle Corps crossing creek, unknown location, circa 1897 (Box 4, Photo number 672-237)
- 25th Infantry Bicycle Corps walking bicycles through field, unknown location, circa 1897 (Box 4, Photo number 672-238)
- 25th Infantry Bicycle Corps carrying bicycles across creek, unknown location, circa 1897 (Box 4, Photo number 672-239)
- 25th Infantry Bicycle Corps walking bicycles down railroad tracks, unknown location, circa 1897 (Box 4, Photo number 672-240)
- Phil and Anna Beckwith, circa 1900 (Box 4, Photo number 672-241)
- Phil and Anna Beckwith, circa 1900 (Box 4, Photo number 672-242)
- Phil and Anna Beckwith, circa 1900 (Box 4, Photo number 672-243)
- Edward Boos?, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-244)
- Group of unidentified people sitting outside, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-245)
- Unidentified people standing on dock, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-246)
- Unidentified people standing near crater, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-247)
- Unidentified people at a scenic viewpoint, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-248)
- Unidentified man and women, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-249)
- Unidentified people gathered around a crater, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-250)
- Unidentified men and women, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-251)
- Unidentified people sitting in grass, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-252)
- Unidentified women observing clouds of smoke, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-253)
- Unidentified people gathered, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-254)
- Unidentified woman sitting against pole, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-255)
- Unidentified people standing on rocky terrain, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-256)
- Unidentified people sitting in grass, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-257)
- Unidentified people on hill, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-258)
- Unidentified people standing on rocks, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-259)
- Unidentified men, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-260)
- Unidentified people sitting outside, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-261)
- Unidentified people gathered around a crater, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-262)
- Unidentified man and woman sitting on rocks, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-263)
- Unidentified woman sitting in a field, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-264)
- Unidentified women, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-265)
- Unidentified people climbing up a rocky hill, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-266)
- Unidentified man, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-267)
- Unidentified man standing near river, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-268)
- Unidentified people, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-269)
- Unidentified people, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-270)
- Unidentified people gathered around 25th Infantry Bicycle Corps, circa 1897 (Box 4, Photo number 672-271)
- Unidentified mountain, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-272)
- Unidentified women in garden, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-273)
- Unidentified man near waterfall, unknown location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-274)
- Unidentified river, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-275)
- Unidentified mountain, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-276)
- Unidentified mountain, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-277)
- Native Americans on horseback, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-278)
- Unidentified men on ice, with cameras, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-279)
- The Dance Audience, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-280)
  Duplicate of DPL# BS-7
- Louis Charlemain, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-281)
  Duplicate of DPL# BS-3
- Round-up, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-282)
  Duplicate of DPL# BS-47
- Indian Village, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-283)
  Duplicate of DPL# BS-51
- Rattlesnake, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-284)
  Duplicate of DPL# BS-52
- Rations for all, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-285)
  Duplicate of DPL# BS-62
- Pierre Paul, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-286)
  Duplicate of DPL# BS-63
- Wallflowers, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-287)
  Duplicate of DPL# BS-65
- Isadore Sorell's Sweathouse, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-288)
  Duplicate of DPL# BS-77
- Mission Falls, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-289)
  Duplicate of DPL# BS-118
- Clara and Family at place where her brother was killed, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-290)
  Duplicate of DPL# BS-105
- Missoula Mercantile Company Parade, July 4th, Man, woman, girl in decorated car, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-291)
- Missoula Mercantile Company Parade, July 4th, Man, 4 girls in decorated car, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-292)
- Missoula Mercantile Company Parade, July 4th, Horse drawn wagon draped with flags, 4 men, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-293)
- Missoula Mercantile Company Parade, July 4th, Horse drawn fire wagon, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-294)
- Missoula Mercantile Company Parade, July 4th, Flag Carrier, drummer, and ?, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-296)
- Missoula Mercantile Company Parade, July 4th, Eagle Float, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-297)
- Missoula Mercantile Company Parade, July 4th, Lg. Missoula Mercantile Company Float, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-298)
- Missoula Mercantile Company Parade, July 4th, Missoula Mercantile Company Float, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-299)
- Missoula Mercantile Company, Parade, July 4th, Missoula Mercantile Company Float, Saddles, Harness, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-300)
- Missoula Mercantile Company, Store front from left, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-301)
- Missoula Mercantile Company, Store front close-up, MHS display, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-302)
- Missoula Mercantile Company, Store front from right, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-303)
- Home pictures, Tulip garden with trellis, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-304)
- Home pictures, Tulip garden with fountain, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-305)
- Home pictures, Corner of Room, Indian Baskets, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-306)
- Daly Ranch Horses, Full horse, nose cut out of picture, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-307)
- Daly Ranch Horses, Horse's head, First Premium Ribbon, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-308)
- Daly Ranch Horse, Full Horse, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-309)
- Unidentified group, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/1, Photo number 672-310)
- Unidentified hot spring, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/1, Photo number 672-311)
- Undentified lake, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/1, Photo number 672-312)
- Unidentified Rock Pile (?), Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/1, Photo number 672-313)
- Unidentified people, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/1, Photo number 672-314)
- Geyser, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/1, Photo number 672-315)
- Geyser, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/1, Photo number 672-316)
- Unidentified man and woman, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/1, Photo number 672-317)
- Undentified River, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/1, Photo number 672-318)
- Unidentified River, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/1, Photo number 672-319)
- Unidentified River and Mountain, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/1, Photo number 672-320)
- Waterfall, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/1, Photo number 672-321)
- Unidentified River, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/1, Photo number 672-322)
- Geyser, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/1, Photo number 672-323)
- Geyser, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/1, Photo number 672-324)
- Geyser, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/1, Photo number 672-325)
- Geyser, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/2, Photo number 672-326)
- Geyser, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/2, Photo number 672-327)
- Geyser, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/2, Photo number 672-328)
- Unidentified people at hot spring, Yellowstone national Park, undated (Box-folder 5/2, Photo number 672-329)
- Clouds of smoke, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/2, Photo number 672-330)
- Burnt forest area, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/2, Photo number 672-331)
- Geyser, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/2, Photo number 672-332)
- Horse-drawn buggy on Mt. Road, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/2, Photo number 672-333)
- Unidentified Mountain, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/2, Photo number 672-334)
- Unidentified geyser, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/2, Photo number 672-335)
- Unidentified rock formation, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/2, Photo number 672-336)
- Unidentified rock formation, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/2, Photo number 672-337)
- Unidentified lake, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/2, Photo number 672-338)
- Unidentified women standing on rock, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/2, Photo number 672-339)
- Unidentified rock formation, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/2, Photo number 672-340)
- Unidentified rock formation, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/3, Photo number 672-341)
- Unidentified people by pool of water, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/3, Photo number 672-342)
- Unidentified rock formation, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/3, Photo number 672-343)
- Unidentified rock formation, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/3, Photo number 672-344)
- Unidentified people on porch steps, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/3, Photo number 672-345)
- Unidentified Inn, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/3, Photo number 672-346)
- Geyser, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/3, Photo number 672-347)
- Unidentified rock formation, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/3, Photo number 672-348)
- Unidentified rock formation, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/3, Photo number 672-349)
- Unidentified people watching geyser, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/3, Photo number 672-350)
- Unidentified pool of water, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/3, Photo number 672-351)
- Unidentified people by hot spring, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/3, Photo number 672-352)
- Unidentified waterfall, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/3, Photo number 672-353)
- Geyser, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/3, Photo number 672-354)
- Unidentified rock formation, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/3, Photo number 672-355)
- Unidentified rock formation, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/3, Photo number 672-356)
- Unidentified lake, Yellowstone National Park, undated (Box-folder 5/3, Photo number 672-357)
- Unidentified people riding horses, undated (Box-folder 5/4, Photo number 672-358)
- Unidentified people riding horses, undated (Box-folder 5/4, Photo number 672-359)
- Unidentified people riding horses through Native American campground, undated (Box-folder 5/4, Photo number 672-360)
- Unidentified people riding horses, undated (Box-folder 5/4, Photo number 672-361)
- Unidentified people riding horses, undated (Box-folder 5/4, Photo number 672-362)
- Unidentified people on horses, undated (Box-folder 5/4, Photo number 672-363)
- Unidentified people on horses, undated (Box-folder 5/4, Photo number 672-364)
- Unidentified people on horses, undated (Box-folder 5/4, Photo number 672-365)
- Unidentified people riding horses, undated (Box-folder 5/4, Photo number 672-366)
- Unidentified people riding horses (Racing?), undated (Box-folder 5/4, Photo number 672-367)
- Unidentified people on horses, undated (Box-folder 5/4, Photo number 672-368)
- Unidentified people riding horses (Racing?), undated (Box-folder 5/4, Photo number 672-369)
- Horse race, undated (Box-folder 5/4, Photo number 672-370)
- Unidentified people riding horses through Native American campground, undated (Box-folder 5/4, Photo number 672-371)
- Unidentified Native Americans sitting on ground near tipi, undated (Box-folder 5/4, Photo number 672-372)
- Two Indian children near unidentified creek, undated (Box-folder 5/5, Photo number 672-373)
- Native American child standing by unidentified creek, undated (Box-folder 5/5, Photo number 672-374)
  Duplicate of 672-380
- Unidentified person on wagon; tipis in background, undated (Box-folder 5/6, Photo number 672-375)
- Unidentified men in front of tipi, undated (Box-folder 5/6, Photo number 672-376)
- Chines-Telkami (Indian dance), undated (Box-folder 5/6, Photo number 672-377)
- The Parade, undated (Box-folder 5/6, Photo number 672-378)
- Tipis, undated (Box-folder 5/6, Photo number 672-379)
- Native American child standing by unidentified creek, undated (Box-folder 5/7, Photo number 672-380)
  Duplicate of 672-374
- "Wallflowers #1" Native Americans on horseback gathered around structure, some on wagons, undated (Box-folder 5/7, Photo number 672-381)
- "Native Americans on Horseback" Native Americans gathered around structure, undated (Box-folder 5/7, Photo number 672-382)
- Scenic photo of trees and unidentified creek, undated (Box-folder 5/7, Photo number 672-383)
- Skipped Number, undated (Box-folder 5, Photo number 672-384)
- Skipped Number, undated (Box-folder 5, Photo number 672-385)
- Glacier Peak, Upper Rattlesnake, undated (Box-folder 5/8, Photo number 672-386)
- In the Pasture, undated (Box-folder 5/8, Photo number 672-387)
  Duplicate of 78-390
- A Haunt for Ducks, undated (Box-folder 5/8, Photo number 672-388)
  Duplicate of 78-434
- Bonner Dam, undated (Box-folder 5/8, Photo number 672-389)
  Duplicate of 78-391 & DPL# B-198
- On the Road to Ovando, undated (Box-folder 5/8, Photo number 672-390)
  Duplicate of 78-380
- Big Four Blocks, undated (Box-folder 5/8, Photo number 672-391)
- Missoula, South side, undated (Box-folder 5/8, Photo number 672-392)
- Mission Range, undated (Box-folder 5/8, Photo number 672-393)
- Mission Range and clouds, undated (Box-folder 5/8, Photo number 672-394)
  Duplicate of 78-427
- Vermilion Gorge, undated (Box-folder 5/8, Photo number 672-395)
  Duplicate of 78-436
- In the Woods, undated (Box-folder 5/8, Photo number 672-396)
  Duplicate of 78-394
- A Place for Trout, undated (Box-folder 5/8, Photo number 672-397)
- Sunset, Flathead Lake, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-398)
- Moonlight on Flathead Lake, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-399)
- Mission Creek and McDonald Peak, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-400)
  Duplicate of 78-341
- Buffalo Veterans, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-401)
- On the Flathead, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-402)
  Duplicate of 78-424
- Vermilion Creek Falls, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-403)
  Duplicate of 78-458
- Dry Lake, Flathead Valley, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-404)
  Duplicate of 78-405
- On the way to Kalispell, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-405)
- Sunshine and Shadow (Marshall Grade), undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-406)
  Duplicate of 78-332
- The Days Work Done, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-407)
- Haying, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-408)
  Duplicate of 78-346
- Round-up scene, Bunching up, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-409)
- A Flathead Homestead, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-410)
- Hellgate Canyon, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-411)
  Duplicate of 78-453
- New Years Day, Rattlesnake, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-412)
  Duplicate of 78-428
- Missoula and Jumbo, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-413)
- Rattlesnake in winter, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-414)
- Rattlesnake in winter, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-415)
  Duplicate of 78-419
- Missing, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-416)
- The Rustic Shrine, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-417)
  Duplicate of 78-251
- Big Blackfoot River, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-418)
- Sunset, Pine Street, Missoula, undated (Box-folder 5/9, Photo number 672-419)
- Two calves on dirt road with lodgepole fence alongside, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-421)
- Pend'Oreille Falls, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-422)
  Duplicate of 78-336
- Indian fishing, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-423)
  Duplicate of 78-252
- Pend'Oreille Falls, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-424)
- Pend'Oreille Falls, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-425)
- View from foot of Flathead Lake, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-426)
- The Steamer Kalispell in a fog, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-427)
- Camp Point Bay, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-428)
- Arrowhead Beach, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-429)
  Duplicate of 78-449
- Swamp Creek, Flathead Valley, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-430)
  Duplicate of 78-409
- Lake Blaine, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-431)
  Duplicate of 78-407
- Wash day on the Lake, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-432)
- Water Nymphs, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-433)
- Missing, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-434)
- Among the Islands, Flathead Lake, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-435)
  Duplicate of 78-406
- Pend'Oreille Falls, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-436)
- Flathead River, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-437)
  Duplicate of 78-363
- Flathead River, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-438)
  Duplicate of 78-413
- Flathead River, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-439)
  Duplicate of 78-414
- Flathead River, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-440)
  Duplicate of 78-364
- Swamp Creek, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-441)
  Duplicate of 78-410
- Rainbow in the evening, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-442)
  Duplicate of 78-400
- The Man with the Scythe, undated (Box-folder 6/1, Photo number 672-443)
- Skating on the Rattlesnake, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-444)
  Duplicate of 78-412
- Shinney on the Rattlesnake, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-445)
  Duplicate of 78-359
- Buffalo, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-446)
- Buffalo, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-447)
- An Indian Ranch, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-448)
- Lake McDonald, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-449)
- Lake McDonald, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-450)
- Unidentified waterfall, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-451)
- Unidentifed women walking on dirt road (unknown location), undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-452)
- Cloudy day on Mission Creek, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-453)
- Pend'Oreille Falls, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-454)
- A Pine Forest, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-455)
- Sterling's Front Walk, Missoula, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-456)
  Duplicate of 78-417
- Lower Falls, Lightning Creek, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-457)
  Duplicate of 78-459
- Big Blackfoot River, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-458)
  Duplicate of 78-420
- Round-up scene, holding the bunch, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-459)
- Bridal Veil Falls, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-460)
- Cascade Falls, Lightning Creek, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-461)
- Peaks on the Mission Range, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-462)
  Duplicate of 78-460
- Mission Creek, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-463)
- Elizabeth Falls of Mission Creek, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-464)
  Duplicate of 78-425
- Pend'Oreille Falls, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-465)
- Mission Creek, undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-466)
- Crack the Whip (Rattlesnake), undated (Box-folder 6/2, Photo number 672-467)
  Duplicate of 78-356
- Unidentified mountain, undated (Box-folder 6/3, Photo number 672-468)
- Unidentified mountain, undated (Box-folder 6/3, Photo number 672-469)
- On Lake Blaine, undated (Box-folder 6/3, Photo number 672-470)
- Unidentified mountain, undated (Box-folder 6/3, Photo number 672-471)
- Unidentified rock, undated (Box-folder 6/3, Photo number 672-472)
- A Shady Nook, undated (Box-folder 6/3, Photo number 672-473)
  Duplicate of 78-366
- A Rustic on the Bridge on the Rattlesnake, undated (Box-folder 6/3, Photo number 672-474)
  Duplicate of 78-457